Lowell Thomas Jr.
Marist Archives and Special Collections
- Lowell Thomas Jr., 2.1.3.3.4
  - Lowell Thomas, Jr.: United States Navy's goodwill tour of South America with photographer Bonney Powell and Lowell Thomas, Jr., 1939; 3 (Box 1531)
    - [Group of men in uniform saluting], 33
    - [Man looking out at sea], 34
    - [Luggage(?) coming off of a ship], 35
    - [View down a body of water], 36
    - [Man in uniform posing], 37
    - [View from the ship], 38
    - [View of the sky], 39
    - [View of a ship], 40
    - [View of a ship from a port-hole], 41
    - [View of a ship from a port-hole], 42
    - [View from the ship], 43
    - [View of a ship], 44
    - [Injured(?) man], 45